Felipe Bevilacqua – (age 27)

Date of birth: 10/07/1987

Address: 1414 Mazzei Av. - ap. 141 City: Sao Paulo – SP – Brazil

CEP: 02310-002

Home Phone: +55 (11) 2206-1220 Cell phone: +55 (11) 97600-4400 E-mail: contact@felipebevi.com.br Personal Portifolio: http://felipebevi.com

Interest

PHP developer systems

Summary of Curriculum

12 years in the area, I have knowledge and experience in C, PHP and JAVA; have extensive knowledge of new tools and frameworks. I've worked with databases MySQL and SQL Server 2008, SCRUM organization; ease of working code in production management versioning in SVN / GIT, consolidated into Magento, Wordpress, jQuery, ZEND, CSS3, HTML5 and responsive design experiences. Environments Apache, Ubuntu, NGINX and Windows. Now I'm programmer in Objective C to developer Apple applications.

I plan live in other country a during 1 or 2 years to be better in my professional profile and learn other cultures and experiences with my family (my wife and my 2 little sons).

Specializations

Installation and Maintenance of microcomputers - Computer City - 3 months - 2000

English - CCAA - São Paulo - SP - 4 years - 1998 to 2002 - Conclusion

English - Wisdom - São Paulo - SP - 1 year - 2003 - Completed

PHP with MySQL - Essentials - Senac - Consolation - 30 hours - 2005 -

JavaCard - FIAP - 30 hours - 2006 - Completed

Ajax with PHP and JSP - FIAP - 16 hours - 2008 - Completed

Keep as a hobby in the Arduino development platform (C). Developing personal projects for home automation and smart products for external companies.

Professional experience (descending order)

ESTADÃO - Journal (www.estadao.com) - 10/2014 to current job

Analyst Programmer PHP

Creation of a centralized system of information entities called Taxonomy, for control, enrichment and provision of information for all production data channels as journalists, blogging, writing and internet portals. Controlled by Jira SCRUM and versioning of files via GIT and SVN, currently develop interfaces to web services, records and control IPTC codes. Developed in January 2015 a plugin for Wordpress to consume the APIs and WebServices created, as well as validate and suggest tags for the blog text in Wordpress. Right now I'm working on another project to establish a system called Polopoly, which is based on Java and Maven. Creating modules, customizing the product and integrating with other internal platforms, including Taxonomy which I created here.

CAMPANHA DIGITAL - 2 months - 08/2014 to 10/2014

Analyst Programmer PHP

Maintenance of websites and internal company systems, social application development for IOS mirror site www.transportedecente.com.br and the creation of sites for political candidates: www.camposmachado.com.br, www.marlenesenadora.com.br, www.drmachado.com.br, www.policeneto.com.br. Using PHP with MySQL and Wordpress, as well as customization of modules, including some items as HTML5 audio in the background and integration plan with the Facebook API aa pair creating Fanpages (iframes within Facebook for the site), integrating platforms officers with social media.

LEMA21 (www.lema21.com.br) - 4 months - 03/2014 to 07/2014

Programmer Analyst Sr. PHP

Creation of new features and maintenance of the company www.lema21.com.br, an e-commerce site based on <u>Magento</u>, developing solutions NGINX with MySQL servers. Change templates in MVC structure, creating new layouts and modules and integrated into the system reports.

THOMSON REUTERS - 1 year and 8 months - 04/2012 to 12/2013

• Sr. PHP Programmer Analyst - Last post - 04/2012 the 12/2013 - 1 year and 8 months

After the acquisition of FISCO Soft by Thomson Reuters had key role in the migration and conversion of data from over 10 million records from the local database to the new world system. Actively participating in daily meetings and conferences between Spain, USA and Argentina (listening and answering questions in Spanish and English). Worked on implementation of SCRUM for work and organization of the new development team. All this in 10 months to complete a product of worldwide named Checkpoint (Brazil), which is already used by all the 100 largest companies in the USA. 85% of the information of this new system, were migrated from FISCO Soft under my coordination.

FISCO SOFT EDITORA LTDA (www.fiscosoft.com.br) - 1 year and 1 month - 03/2011 to 04/2012

• Sr. PHP Programmer Analyst - Last post - 06/2011 the 04/2012 - 10 months

Schedule and lead the team (6 developers with PHP) in the development of daily tasks, centralize and distribute the calls of the customers and control / document the hours spent with each project within the company by programmer.

• Sr. PHP Programmer - Penultimate position - 03/2011 to 06/2011 - 3 months

Responsible for development and maintenance of websites in PHP company. Provide ongoing maintenance of the site Fiscosoft.com.br and their products (Decisoes.com.br, Comexdata.com.br, Systax.com.br, Isstotal.com.br, prefeituraeletronica.com.br, mundocontabil.com. br, prefeituraeletronica.com.br, mundocontabil.com. br, prefeituraeletronica.com. prefe

CATHO ONLINE (www.catho.com.br) - 1 year - 01/2010 to 01/2011

• Senior Programmer PHP Mysql - Last post - 01/2010 to 01/2011 - 1 year Responsible for developing new solutions and resolutions of technical problems throughout the site CareerBuilder and its internal systems. Among these, we highlight all the new development area subscribers and website http://cadastro.catho.com.br. Worked with SCRUM methodology and object orientation.

INNANZI TECHNOLOGY AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS - 4 months - 06/2009 to 10/2009

• Telecommunications Analyst - Last post - 06/2009 to 10/2009 - 4 months

Management and maintenance of IPBX systems (Linux, asterisk); responsible for all the needs, requests and reports in the field of telecommunications (based on PHP and MySQL), backup routines, seeking and implementing new technologies, monitoring the data link and E1. Developing new solutions as well as integration with particular systems with front-end in PHP / MySQL.

FOCO TELECOM & NETWORKING LTDA - 1 year - 06/2008 to 06/2009

Analyst Developer PHP / JAVA / PERL - Last post - 06/2008 the 06/2009 - 1 year

Updating and creating interface for Linux-based telephony system called Asterisk, enabling seamless integration and control of the system by users, as well as statistical and operational controls through functions and routines created via interface using PHP and Ajax. Creating an auto-dial system, monitoring and statistical extensions to a complete phone system reports.

PRIME SOLUTION - 2 months - 04/2008 to 06/2008

• PHP Programmer Analyst - Last post - 04/2008 the 06/2008 - 2 months

Responsible for all PHP development company; contributions in the development of 80% of the site: www.valeriotrabanco.com and by tweaking the company's website.

IBM BRAZIL - International Business Machines - 3 months - 10/2007 to 01/2008

• Java Programmer Analyst - Last post - 01/2008 to 10/2007 - 3 months

Responsible for the analysis and development of a Java-based solution that integrates with Mainframe; which generated daily reports of all ATMs of the ABN (Real) to Brazil level. Task performed 1 hour before all performed by a sector of 10 people per day.

OVER FLASH WEB DESIGN INFORMÁTICA LTDA - 2 years and 6 months - 01/2005 to 07/2007

• Delphi Programmer Analyst / PHP - Last post - 01/2005 the 07/2007 - 2 years and 6 months

Responsible for 50% of creating a whole ERP system based in Delphi7 for logistics management and a module, this same system in PHP that allows customers of these companies consult stock and deliveries in real time via internet.

DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION STATE OF SAO PAULO (SEESP-SP) - 9 months - 03/2004 to 12/2004

• Web Designer - Last post - 03/2004 to 12/2004 - 9 months

Initiated the development of the Secretariat sites, earning that year a contest to design the best government websites; I was responsible for 100% of website development www.drhu.sp.gov.br and after this experience, I dedicated myself to experience in support of the Secretariat.

Training

Undergraduate # 1

Institution: FIAP - Faculty of Informatics and Adm Paulista.

Training level: Undergraduate

Course Name: Baccalaureate in Information Systems

Current year: already formed

Start date: 01/2005

Completion date: 12/2008

Undergraduate # 2

Institution: Senac

Degree of training: Technician

Course Name: Computer Technician

Current year: already formed

Start date: 01/2003

Date of completion: 09/2004

Extracurricular # 1

Institution: IMPACTA Technology Degree of training: Technician Course name: **iOS Development** Current year: already formed

Start date: 06/2014

Date of completion: 12/2014